Finding Aid for Men's Glee Club (University of Michigan) records 1886-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sound Recordings
  - Reel-to-Reel Tapes
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 120th Annual Spring Concert, 1979 April 07; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-73-1-1-1]; mp3 file; (The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Non Vos Relinquam Orphanos; Chorus of Prisoners; Rondeau; Selections of Spirituals; No Man Is an Island; Hallelujah, Amen; Encore. Selections by the Friars: Du, du liegst mir im Herzen; What Shall We Do With the Drunken Sailor; Aura Lee; Mood Indigo; What I Did For Love; The Lost Chord; Michigan Songs; The Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-73-1-1-2]; mp3 file; (The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Non Vos Relinquam Orphanos; Chorus of Prisoners; Rondeau; Selections of Spirituals; No Man Is an Island; Hallelujah, Amen; Encore. Selections by the Friars: Du, du liegst mir im Herzen; What Shall We Do With the Drunken Sailor; Aura Lee; Mood Indigo; What I Did For Love; The Lost Chord; Michigan Songs; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - The Friars "Quadraphenomena" Pressing Master, 1979 June 20, 27, 29; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 15 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-74-1-1]; mp3 file; (First Side: Hurry Sundown; Blue Moon; If; The Sunshine Girl; Java Jive; What Are You Doing The Rest of Your Life?; Ding Dong Daddy From Dumas; The Way We Were; Operator. Second side: Sha-Boom; Brother, Can You Spare a Dime?: Who Put The Bomp?; Momma Look Sharp; What I Did For Love; My Little Darlin'; Send in the Clowns; King Tut.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 120th Fall Concert & Wayne State University Men's Glee Club, 1979 November 17; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-75-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Wayne State Glee Club performs: Trosterin Musik; At the Round Earth's Imagined Corners; Salvation Belongeth To our God; Quatre Petite Prieres; Jubilate Deo Omnis Terra. Selections by The Four Muscatels: Haec Est Dies; I Dream of Jeannie; Deep River; Everytime I Feel the Spirit.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-75-2-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Michigan Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Sing, Make a Joyful Noise; Ave Maria; Tarantella; Love and Wine; The Bachelor. Selections by The Friars: Steal Away; Honey Brown; You'll Never Walk Alone; Michigan Songs; The Omnipotence. Alma Maters by Combined Glee Clubs: Hymn to Wayne; The Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-75-2-1-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Michigan Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Sing, Make a Joyful Noise; Ave Maria; Tarantella; Love and Wine; The Bachelor. Selections by The Friars: Steal Away; Honey Brown; You'll Never Walk Alone; Michigan Songs; The Omnipotence. Alma Maters by Combined Glee Clubs: Hymn to Wayne; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club, University of Michigan Symphony Orchestra, & University of Michigan Chamber Orchestra, 1980 April 13; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-76-1-1]; mp3 file; (UM Glee Club Presentation at the International Brahms Festival in Detroit, Rinaldo Opus 50.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 120th Annual Spring Concert, 1980 April 19; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-77-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Veni Sancte Spiritus; Avenging and Bright; The Parting Glass; If I Got My Ticket; The Last Words of David; Selections by The Friars: Go Lovely Rose; Haul Away Joe; There is Nothing Like a Dame; Pore Jud; Blow High! Blow Low!; You'll Never Walk Alone; Son of a Gambolier; Michigan Songs; The Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-77-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Veni Sancte Spiritus; Avenging and Bright; The Parting Glass; If I Got My Ticket; The Last Words of David; Selections by The Friars: Go Lovely Rose; Haul Away Joe; There is Nothing Like a Dame; Pore Jud; Blow High! Blow Low!; You'll Never Walk Alone; Son of a Gambolier; Michigan Songs; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - The Friar's Silver Anniversary, 1980 November 15; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-78-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Friars perform: Laudes Atque Carmina; O Magnum Mysterium; Chorus of Students; The Vagabond; Let Beauty Awake; I Hear an Army; Red Iron Ore; Somebody Callin' My Name; Ev'ry Time I Feel the Spirit; Traces; No One's Perfect.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-78-2-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Prior Friars (Alumni of the Friars) perform: Casey's Coffin; I'll Ne'er Forget My College Days; Varsity; Hail to the Victors; The Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-78-2-1-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Friars perform: Laudes Atque Carmina; O Magnum Mysterium; Chorus of Students; (Duey Medley) The Vagabond; Let Beauty Awake; I Hear an Army; Red Iron Ore; Somebody Callin' My Name; Ev'ry Time I Feel the Spirit; Traces; No One's Perfect.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club "Songs of Michigan", 1981 May 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 15 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-79-1-1]; mp3 file; (A selection of Michigan songs are performed by the University of Michigan Men's Glee Club)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 122nd Fall Concert & Ohio State University Men's Glee Club, 1981 November 21; 3 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-80-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 3; The Ohio State Glee Club performs: Brothers, Sing On; O Filii et Filiae; Come Again, Sweet Love; My Eternal King; Hallelujah, Amen; He Ain't Heavy, He's My Brother; Vive L'Amour; The Wiffenpoof Song; A-Roving; The Buckeye Battle Cry; Campus Echoes.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-80-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 3; The Michigan Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Festgesang an die Kunstler; Songs of Peace; Remember Me; Na gorushke, na gore; Someone To Watch Over Me.)
      - [Tape 3, Part 1], [87250-SR-80-3-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 3 of 3; The Friars perform: Deep River; Soon Ah Will Be Done; Michigan Medley; The Friars Song; The Bum Army; Go Blue; Varsity-Victors. Alma Maters by the Combined Glee Clubs: Carmen Ohio; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 123rd Fall Concert Dedicated to Phillip Duey, 1982 November 13; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-81-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Glory Be To God; Geisterchor; Nachtgesang im Walde; Tribute to P. Duey; The Heart Worships; The Minstrel Boy; Honey L' il Eyes; She is My Slender Small Love; I Wan' to Be Ready; Gershwin Medley. Selections by The Friars: Lowlands; Witness; Michigan Songs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 123rd Fall Concert Dedicated to Phillip Duey, 1982 November 13; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-81-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Glory Be To God; Geisterchor; Nachtgesang im Walde; Tribute to P. Duey; The Heart Worships; The Minstrel Boy; Honey L' il Eyes; She is My Slender Small Love; I Wan' to Be Ready; Gershwin Medley. Selections by The Friars: Lowlands; Witness; Michigan Songs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & The California State University, Hayward, 1983 Spring; 2Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-82-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs a selection of unlisted songs with the California State University Glee Club)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-82-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs a selection of unlisted songs with the California State University Glee Club)
    - 27th Best Concert Ever The Friars and The Grunyons, 1983 March 25; 4 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-83-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 4; Selections by the Friars and the Grunyons: Chant; Darlin'; Pina; Mood Indigo; Blue Moon; Commercial; Bomp; I Do; Have You Seen Her; Java Jive; Tatse or What I Did; Come Go With Me; Let Me Call You Sweetheart; Take You Back; At The Hop; Hangman; Sh-Boom; Dreamer's Ball; He Ain't Heavy; Zombie; Operator; Disney; Tut; Trickle.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-83-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 4; Selections by the Friars and the Grunyons: Chant; Darlin'; Pina; Mood Indigo; Blue Moon; Commercial; Bomp; I Do; Have You Seen Her; Java Jive; Tatse or What I Did; Come Go With Me; Let Me Call You Sweetheart; Take You Back; At The Hop; Hangman; Sh-Boom; Dreamer's Ball; He Ain't Heavy; Zombie; Operator; Disney; Tut; Trickle.)
      - [Tape 3, Part 1], [87250-SR-83-3-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 3 of 4; Selections by the Friars and the Grunyons: Chant; Darlin'; Pina; Mood Indigo; Blue Moon; Commercial; Bomp; I Do; Have You Seen Her; Java Jive; Tatse or What I Did; Come Go With Me; Let Me Call You Sweetheart; Take You Back; At The Hop; Hangman; Sh-Boom; Dreamer's Ball; He Ain't Heavy; Zombie; Operator; Disney; Tut; Trickle.)
      - [Tape 4, Part 1], [87250-SR-83-4-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 4 of 4; Selections by the Friars and the Grunyons: Chant; Darlin'; Pina; Mood Indigo; Blue Moon; Commercial; Bomp; I Do; Have You Seen Her; Java Jive; Tatse or What I Did; Come Go With Me; Let Me Call You Sweetheart; Take You Back; At The Hop; Hangman; Sh-Boom; Dreamer's Ball; He Ain't Heavy; Zombie; Operator; Disney; Tut; Trickle.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 123rd Annual Spring Concert, 1983 November 16; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-84-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Veni Sancte Spiritus; Quatre Petites Prieres de Saint Francoise D'Assise; Nachthelle; Glory Be to God; In Taberna; Vive L' Amour; Lowlands; I Wan' to Be Ready.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-84-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Selections by The Friars: Goddess of the Inland Seas; Blue Book Blues; Ann Arbor Days; Sophisticated Lady; Witness; Ev'ry Time I Feel The Spirit; Songs of the University of Michigan.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 124th Annual Spring Concert, 1984 April 07; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-85-1-1-1]; mp3 file; (The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Tollite Hosias; Brothers, Sing On; Invocation; Psaume 121; The Night Has a Thousand Eyes; Canticle; Only In a Dream. Selections by The Friars: Blues in the Nicht; The Boatmen's Dance; The Parting Glass; Soon-Ah Will Be Done; Songs of the University of Michigan.)
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-85-1-1-2]; mp3 file; (The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Tollite Hosias; Brothers, Sing On; Invocation; Psaume 121; The Night Has a Thousand Eyes; Canticle; Only In a Dream. Selections by The Friars: Blues in the Nicht; The Boatmen's Dance; The Parting Glass; Soon-Ah Will Be Done; Songs of the University of Michigan.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 125th Anniversary Pressing Master, 1984 April 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 15 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-86-1-1]; mp3 file; (Recording date: 1984 April 14; Pressing dates: 1984 June 25, July 02. The Men's Glee Club performs: The Last Words of David; A Dirge for Two Veterans; Invocation; Nachtgesang im Walde; Only in the Dream; Salvation is Created; Veni Sancte Spiritus; Psalme 121; Tollite Hostias.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 125th Fall Concert and Reunion Concert, 1984 November 10; 4 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-87-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 4; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laude Atque Carmina; Let Beauty Awake; The Infinite Shining Heavens; The Pasture; Hymne; Festgesang an die Kunstler.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-87-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 4; The Men's Glee Club performs: No gorushke, Na gore; Au Fond du Temple Saint. Selections by The Arbors: Soon Ah Will Be Done.)
      - [Tape 3, Part 1], [87250-SR-87-3-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 3 of 4; Selections by The Friars and Friars Alumni: Mood Indigo; Laudes Atque Carmina; Soliloquy; Vive L' Amour.)
      - [Tape 4, Part 1], [87250-SR-87-4-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 4 of 4; The Glee Club with Alumni perform Michigan Songs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 125th Annual Spring Concert, 1985 April 13; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-88-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape experienced demagnetization sometime during it's lifetime, audio cuts in and out during certain portions.Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Confitemini Domino; The Bandits' Chorus; Truth Shall Deliver; The Crusaders in Pskov; A Rovin'; Swansea Town; What Shall We Do With a Drunken Sailor?; Branden Scene from the Damnation of Faust.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-88-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape experienced demagnetization sometime during it's lifetime, audio cuts in and out during certain portions. Tape 2 of 2; Selections by The Friars: Someone to Watch Over Me; Mood Indigo; Vive L' Amour; Michigan Songs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club Christmas Master Tape, 1974 September 26; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 15 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-89-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 1; Original Recording Date: 1974 September 26; Pressing date: 1985 October 14O Come, O Come, Emmanuel; Patapan; The Christmas Song; Behold That Star; O Tannenbaum; Silent Night; Gesu Bambino; Twelve Days After Christmas; O Come All Ye Faithful; God Rest You Merry Gentlemen; O Holy Night; The Boar's Head Carol; I Wonder as I Wander; Winter Wonderland; Carol of the Drum.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 126th Fall Concert with the University of Illinois, 1985 November 23; 3 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-90-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 3; The Illinois Glee Club performs: The Last Words of David; Vere Languores Nostros; Treue Liebe; Widerspruch; Ain' Got Time To Die; All the Things You Are; Big Ten Medley; Allegro from "Water Music.")
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-90-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 3; Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Gloria; Good Friday; Gott Meine Zuversicht; Nachthelle; General William Booth Enters into Heaven; Lisa Lan; Shenandoah; Ride the Chariot.)
      - [Tape 3, Part 1], [87250-SR-90-3-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 3 of 3; Selections by The Friars: I Only Have Eyes for You; Langtan till Laudet; Michigan Songs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 126th Spring Concert, 1986 April 12; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-91-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 126th Spring Concert in 1986. Unlisted content.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-91-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 126th Spring Concert in 1986. Unlisted content.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club, 1986; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-91-3-1]; mp3 file; (Content might be 1986 Spring Concert. Unlisted content.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-91-4-1]; mp3 file; (Content might be 1986 Spring Concert. Unlisted content.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 127th Fall Concert, 1986 November 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-92-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Chanson a Boire; William Tell Overture; Drig, Drig, Drig; The Prisoner's Chorus from Fidelio; The Bandit's Chorus from Ernani; Maria from West Side Story; The Bum Army; Girls, Girls, Girls.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-92-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Friars perform selections of Michigan Songs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 127th Annual Spring Concert, 1987 April 11; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-93-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Inveni David; The Last Words of David; Die Nachtigall; The Prisoner's Chorus from Fidelio; The Bandit's Chorus from Ernani; The Parting Glass; Swansea Town; What Shall We Do With the Drunken Sailor; Girls, Girls, Girls.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-93-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Selections by The Friars: Every Time I Feel the Spirit; There is a Balm in Gilead; Soon Ah Will Be Done; Michigan Songs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 128th Fall Concert with the University of Notre Dame Glee Club, 1987 November 21; 4Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-94-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 4; Notre Dame Glee Club performs: Behold Man; O Magnum Mysterium; O Magnum Mysterium; Blessed Be The Lord; Ode for the Fourth of July; Oliver de Lancey; There is a Balm in Gilead; Keep in the Middle of the Road; The Minstrel Boy; The Ash Grove; The Hike Song; Irish Backs; Notre Dame, We Hail Thee; The Notre Dame Victory March.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-94-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 4; The Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; In Taberna from Carmina Burana; Lass dich nur nichts nicht dauren.)
      - [Tape 3, Part 1, [87250-SR-94-3-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 3 of 4; The Michigan Glee Club performs: The Federal Constitution and Liberty Forever: Laws of God, Revolution, Laws of Man.)
      - [Tape 4, Part 1], [87250-SR-94-4-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 4 of 4; Selections by The Friars: Deep River; Ain' A That Good News; Die Musicanten; Michigan Songs; Notre Dame, Our Mother; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club HiFi Recording Studio, [Undated]; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-97-1-1]; mp3 file; (The Men's Glee Club performs: Let Beaty Awake; The Infinite Shining Heavens; The Heart Worships; A Mighty Fortress is Our God; There is a Balm in Gilead; Good Fellows Be Merry; Hallelujah, Amen; Casey Jones; Clementine.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club, [Undated]; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-98-1-1]; mp3 file; (The Men's Glee Club performs: And the Night Shall Be Filled With Music; Stardust; Dream; Deep Purple; Laura; Did You Ever See a Dream Walking?; In The Still of the Night; The Most Beautiful Girl in the World; C Minor Prelude; The Vagabond; Chorus of Pilgrims; Good Fellows Be Merry; The Victors; Laudes Atque Carmina.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club, 1963 December 09; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-99-1-1]; mp3 file; (The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; My Soul is a Witness; Stomp Your Foot; Schlagen Melodien vom Broadway; There is a Balm in Gilead; Lay Down Doggies.)
- China Concert Tour, 2012
  In May 2012, the Men's Glee Club embarked on a two-week concert tour of the People's Republic of China that included visits to Beijing (May 3 to May 5), Xi'an (May 5 to May 8), Chongquing (May 8 to May 11), Wuhan (May 11 to May 13), and Shanghai (May 13 to May 16). The resulting China Concert Tour series is organized around the itinerary and includes digital images shot by club members in various locales, audio and video footage of performances at major stops and video of various excursions in host cities. The series is organized according to the Glee Club's itinerary; through: Of note is the concert performance given at Ba Shu Secondary School (Chongqing)and visits to notable sites such as the Great Wall, Tiananmen Square, the Forbidden City, and Olympic Park (Beijing).
  - Beijing, May 3-5, 2012
    - Arrival, May 3, 2012
      - Digital images of Glee Clubs Arrival in Beijing
    - Forbidden City, May 4, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club's visit to the Forbidden City
    - Tiananmen Square, May 4, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club's visit to Tiananmen Square
    - Tsinghua University Meng Minwei Concert Hall, May 4, 2012
      - Audio recording of the Men's Glee Club performance at Tsinghua University
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club performance at Tsinghua University
      - Video recording of the Men's Glee Club performance at Tsinghua University
    - Great Wall of China, May 5, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club at the Great Wall of China
      - Video recording of the Men's Glee Club singing at the Great Wall of China
    - Jade Factory, May 5, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club visit to a jade factory in Beijing
    - Olympic Park, May 5, 2012
      - (Digital images of the Men's Glee Club's visit to the site of the Summer Olympic Games., 2008
    - Tea Ceremony, May 5, 2012
      - (Digital images of the Men's Glee Club participating in a tea ceremony
  - Xi'an (May 5 to May 8, 2012)
    - Concert Hall, May 6, 2012
      - Audio recording of the Men's Glee Club performance at Xi'an Concert Hall
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club performance at Xi'an Concert Hall
    - City Wall, May 7, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club visit to the Xi'an city walls
    - Terracotta Warriors, May 7, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club excursion to see the terracotta warriors of Xi'an.
  - Chongqing (May 8 to May 11, 2012)
    - Er Ling Park, May 8, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club tour of Er Ling Park
      - Video recording of the Men's Glee Club tour of Er Ling Park
    - Ba Shu Secondary School, May 9, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club visit to Ba Shu Secondary School
      - Video recordings
        - Men's Glee Club's arrival at Ba Shu Secondary School
        - Ba Shu Secondary School staff remarks
        - Student martial arts demonstration
        - Speeches by Men's Glee Club members, 3 digital files
        - Rehearsal by the Men's Glee Club
        - Vocal performance by the Men's Glee Club, 4 digital files
    - Dazu Stone Carving Park, May 9, 2012
      - Digital images of Men's Glee Club excursion to Dazu Stone Carving Park, a World Heritage Site
    - Dongwuyuan, May 10, 2012
      - (Digital images of the Men's Glee Club's visit to Chongqing Dongquyuan (Zoo
    - Grand Theater, May 10, 2012
      - Audio recording of the Men's Glee Club performance at the Chongqing Grand Theater
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club performance at the Chongqing Grand Theater
      - Video recordings
        - Men's Glee Club tour of the Chongqing Grand Theater
        - Men's Glee Club rehearsal at the Chongqing Grand Theater
  - Wuhan (May 11 to May 13, 2012)
    - Han Kou waterfront on the Yangtze River, May 11, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club excursion to the Han Koue waterfront
    - Hubei Provincial Museum, May 12, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club visit to the Hubei Provincial Museum
    - Qintai Grand Theater, May 12, 2012
      - Audio recording of the Men's Glee Club performance at the Qintai Grand Theater
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club performance at the Qintai Grand Theater
      - Video recordings
        - Men's Glee Club tour of the Qintai Grand Theater
        - Men's Glee Club rehearsal at the Qintai Grand Theater
  - Shanghai (May 13 to May 16, 2012)
    - Oriental Art Center, May 13, 2012
      - Audio recording of the Men's Glee Club performance at the Shanghai Oriental Art Center
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club performance at the Shanghai Oriental Art Center
      - Video recordings
        - Mens' Glee Club rehearsal for concert at the Shanghai Oriental Art Center
        - Mens' Glee Club performance at the Shanghai Oriental Art Center, 6 digital files
        - Post-concert cleanup and mingling at the Shanghai Oriental Art Center